Preliminary Inventory to the Carla A. Hills Papers, 1964-1993
Hoover Institution Archives
- 56. National Governors Conference, 6/10/75 (Box 56)
- 57. National Housing Conference, 2/29/76
- 58. National Housing Rehabilitation Association Conference, 10/2/75
- 59. National League of Cities, 12/3/75
- 60. National Mobile Home Advisory Council, 5/5/75
- 61. National Town Meeting, 9/10/75
- 62. National Urban League, 8/2/76
- 63. New York Women's Bar Association, 6/2/75
- 64. North Carolina Association of Realtors, 10/1/76
- 65. Ohio Municipal League, 9/15/76
- 66. Palo Alto Chamber of Commerce, 10/26/76
- 67. People United to Save Humanity, 8/7/75
- 68. Peoria Rotary Club Luncheon, 3/12/76
- 69. Law School of Pepperdine University Commencement, 5/24/75
- 70. Professional Builder of the Year Award (Dallas), 1/19/76
- 71. Puerto Rico Message from the President, 1/1/77
- 72. Republican National Conference (Washington), 2/6/76
- 73. Republican Women's Forum, 11/21/75
- 74. Stanford University Commencement, 6/13/76
- 75. Time, Inc., 5/3/76
- 76. United States Conference of Mayors, 6/30/76
- 77. United States Conference of Mayors, 7/8/75
- 78. United States League of Savings Association, 11/11/75
- 79. Urban Homesteading Conference, 6/26/75
- 80. Ventura County Federation of Republican Women, 5/26/76 (Box 57)
- 81. Vice President's White House Public Forum (Los Angeles), 12/9/75
- 82. Vice President's White House Public Forum (Tampa), 10/29/75
- 83. Washington Press Club, 9/12/75
- 84. White House Briefing with Conference of Mayors, 1/29/76
- 85. White House Conference on Domestic and Economic Affairs, 9/4/75
- 86. White House Consumer Conference (Kansas City), 1/14/76
- 87. Women in Communications, Inc., 5/23/75
- 88. Women in Housing Conference, 10/18/76
- 89. Women's Lawyers Association of Los Angeles, 9/21/75
- 90. YWCA of New York City, 10/8/76
- The Advocate for Human Services
- AFL-CIO Monthly Housing Newsletter
- Articles in Periodicals (HUD)
- The Black Worker, National Urban League's Research Department Quarterly Economic Report
- Challenge
- Community Development Trends
- Complaint Activity and Compliance Reviews
- Construction Reports
- Current Financial and Housing Developments
- Debarred, Suspended/Ineligible Contractors and Grantees -, 1976
- Debarred, Suspended/Ineligible Contractors and Grantees -, 1975
- Departmental Weekly Reports - Vol. #2 -, 1976
- Departmental Weekly Reports -, 1975
- Drug Enforcement (Box 58)
- Economic Briefs
- Eo Bulletin
- Economic Outlook Report
- Features
- Federal Credit Union
- Gallagher President's Report
- Headquarters Training Opportunities
- HUD International
- Housing Affairs Letter
- Housing and Community Development Act of, 1974
- Housing Production and Marketing
- HUDDLE
- HUD News Releases, July - December, 1976
- HUD News Releases, January - June, 1976
- HUD News Releases, August - December, 1975
- HUD News Releases -, 1975 March - July
- Housing and Urban Affairs Daily - Vol. #7, January 1977 (Box 59)
- Housing and Urban Affairs Daily - Vol. #6, October - December, 1976
- Housing and Urban Affairs Daily - Vol. #5, July - September 1976
- Housing and Urban Affairs Daily - Vol. #4, April - June, 1976
- Housing and Urban Affairs Daily - Vol. #3, January - March, 1976
- Housing and Urban Affairs Daily - Vol. #2, July - December, 1975
- Housing and Urban Affairs Daily - Vol. #1, March - June, 1975
- Impact
- Justice Department News Releases
- LLAA Newsletter
- Legislative Daily - Vol. #5, July - October, 1976
- Legislative Daily - Vol. #4, April - June, 1976
- Legislative Daily - Vol. #3, January - March, 1976
- Legislative Daily - Vol. #2, August - December, 1975
- Legislative Daily - Vol. #1, March - July, 1975
- Legislative Reports - Vol. #1 thru, June, 1976 (Box 60)
- Legislative Reports - Vol. #2 thru, July 1976 October, 1976
- Library
- Merit Staffing - Vacancy Listing
- Mortgage Market Trends and Outlook
- Newsletter HUD, (April 1975-January 1977)
- Recent Development, 1976
- Recent Development, 1975
- Recent Research Reports Research Supported by PD&R
- Scheduled and Planned Hearings Weekly Reports
- Speaking Engagements
- Speeches by Cabinet Members -, 1976 (Box 61)
- Speeches by Cabinet Members -, 1975
- Speeches by Other Cabinet Members -, 1975
- Speeches by Others -, 1975
- Speeches - HUD
  - James H. Blair - Speeches and/or Statements
  - David S. Cook - Speeches and/or Statements
  - H. R. Crawford - Speeches and/or Statements
  - James F. Dausch - Speeches and/or Statements
  - David M. deWilde - Speeches and/or Statements
  - Thomas P. Dunne - Speeches and/or Statements
  - Robert R. Elliott - Speeches and/or Statements
  - Helen Holt - Speeches and/or Statements
  - J. Robert Hunter - Speeches and/or Statements
  - Daniel P. Kearney - Speeches and/or Statements
  - John R. McDowell - Speeches and/or Statements
  - David O. Meeker - Speeches and/or Statements
  - Michael H. Moskow - Speeches and/or Statements
  - Charles J. Orlebeke - Speeches and/or Statements
  - John B. Rhinelander - Speeches and/or Statements
  - Gloria E. A. Toote - Speeches and/or Statements
- Speeches by Others
  - Justice
  - Treasury
  - Federal Reserve Board
  - White House
  - Miscellaneous
- Staff Bulletins (HUD) (Box 62)
- State Bar of California Reports
- Summary of Congressional and Executive Action of Interest to HUD -, 1975
- Telephone Log -, 1975
- Telephone Log-, 1976/7
- Veterans
- Weekend Schedules
- White House News Conference
- Women in Action
- Administrative Conference of the United States Council (Box 63)
- Administrative Conference of the United States - Council/Conference Members
- Administrative Conference of the United States - Miscellaneous
- Administrative Conference of the United States - Meeting, 3/17/75
- Administrative Conference of the United States - Meeting, 5/12/75
- Administrative Conference of the United States - Twelfth Plenary Session
- Administrative Conference of the United States - Correspondence, 1972
- Administration's Economic Policy
- Administrative Office of the United States Courts
- American Judicature Society
- Antitrust Adviser -, 1973
- Applicants
- Brookings Institution -, 1/28/75
- Conference for Business Executives on Federal Government Operations
- California Bankers Association - Bank Presidents Seminar, 1/9-11/75 Santa Barbara, California
- Christmas Party -, 1974
- Commendation Letters
- Comptroller of Currency
- The Conference Board (Box 64)
- Congressional Contacts
- Constitutional Rights Foundation
- Cornell Law School, 10/24-25/74
- Crawford, Clare Articles
- Cystic Fibrosis Foundation
- Domestic Council- Briefing of the Vice President
- Directive Memoranda
- Drug Enforcement
- Ertra, Donald
- Executive Women in Government
- FBA Western Briefing Conference San Francisco, CA - 10/7/74
- Federal Bar Association - Western Regional Conference, San Diego, Federal Rules of Evidence, 11/15-16/74
- Freedom of Information Act
- Government Contracts - Mason & Hanger-Silas Mason Case U. S. Court of Claims No. 616-71
- Government Contracts - Speech Materials
- Housing and Urban Development - HUD
- HUD -- Interstate Land Sales
- HUD Operating Subsidy Cases
- Department of Labor "Compliance, Enforcement/Reporting in U/Labor-Management Reporting/Disclosure Act, 1973
- Law in a Free Society
- Miscellaneous
- National Conference on Appellate Justice, San Diego, CA, 1/23-26/75
- National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs, Inc.
- National Institute for Trial Advocacy - University of Nevada at Reno, 8/2/74
- National Institute of Building Sciences
- National Institute of Justice (ABA Proposal)
- National Lawyers Wives Convention - Honolulu, Hawaii -, 8/13/74
- Investment Committee Meetings
- Report to Congress re Improved Government Assistance Can Increase U.S. Share of Foreign Engineering/Construction Project, 9/9/74
- Report to Congress - Lack of Authority Limits Consumer Protection: Problmes Identifying/Removing from Market Products Which Violate Law, 9/14/72
- Resignation Letters
- Women--Report on Survey of Department Washington-Based Women Employe "The Status of Women in D/J: A Blueprint for Action"
- Women Law Reporter
- Women Lawyers' Association of Los Angeles
- Women's Programs
- Women's Work Magazine
- Yale Law School Fund
- Yale Club
- Yale University - - Problems of Professional Role/Responsibility in the Law Firm, 11/1/74
- Yale University Council Committee on the Law School
- Yale Law Report
- Yale Law Women's Association
- BUDGET (Box 65)
  - BUDGET IMPACT OF EMERGENCY HOUSING ACT OF 1975
  - BUDGET FY 75 OUTLAYS
  - BUDGET FY 76 REPORT AND APPEAL
  - BUDGET FY 76 REPORT/APPEAL VOL. #2
- COMMENDATIONS LETTERS (HUD) -, April 1975 through June 1976
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT BLOCK GRANT PROGRAM - General - Vol. #6, July through September 1976
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT BLOCK GRANT PROGRAM - General - Vol. #5, April through June 1976
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT BLOCK GRANT PROGRAM - General - Vol. #4, February through March 1976
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT BLOCK GRANT PROGRAM - General - Vol. #3, December 1975 - January 1976
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT BLOCK GRANT PROGRAM - General - Vol. #2, September through November, 1975
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT BLOCK GRANT PROGRAM - General - Vol. #1
- SECTION 701 COMPREHENSIVE PLANNING ASSISTANCE PROGRAM - Vol. #2 (Box 66)
- SECTION 701 PLANNING ASSISTANCE - - Vol. #1, March through July, 1975
- CONGRESSIONAL CORRESPONDENCE - Vol., November through December, 1975
- CONGRESSIONAL CORRESPONDENCE - Vol., September through October, 1975
- CONGRESSIONAL CORRESPONDENCE - Vol. #1, March through August, 1975
- EQUAL OPPORTUNITY (Blair) - Through - Vol. #1, June, 1976
- EXECUTIVE SECRETARIAT - Vol. #3 -, June through September, 1976
- EXECUTIVE SECRETARIAT - Vol. #2 -, January through May, 1976
- EXECUTIVE SECRETARIAT - Vol. #1 -, March through December, 1975
- FNMA (Federal National Mortgage Association) - Through - General - Vol. #1, June, 1976
- INVITATIONS (Accepted) Vol. #4, May - August, 1976 (Box 67)
- INVITATIONS (Accepted) Vol. #3, November 1975 - April 1976
- INVITATIONS (Accepted) Vol. #2, August - October, 1975
- INVITATIONS (Accepted) Vol. #1, March - July, 1975
- INVITATIONS (Declined) Vol. #5, May - September, 1976
- INVITATIONS (Declined) Vol. #4, February - April, 1976
- INVITATIONS (Declined) Vol. #3, November 1975 - January 1976
- INVITATIONS (Declined) Vol. #2, August - October 1975
- INVITATIONS (Declined) Vol. #1, March - July 1975
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWS ARTICLES through Vol. #1, September 1976
- NATIONAL MOBILE HOME CONSTRUCTION AND SAFETY STANDARDS - Vol. #1 (Box 68)
- PERSONNEL (Curvey) Vol. #1, March - December 1975
- PUBLIC AFFAIRS - Vol. #4, April - June, 1976
- PUBLIC AFFAIRS - Vol. #3, January - March, 1976
- PUBLIC AFFAIRS - Vol. #2, July - December, 1975
- PUBLIC AFFAIRS - Vol. #1, March - June, 1975
- WHITE HOUSE MEMORANDA - Vol. #2
- WHITE HOUSE MEMORANDA - Vol. #1, March - December, 1975
- Briefing Book - Senate Oversight Hearings --, June 12, 1975 (Box 69)
- Senate Oversight Hearings --, June 12, 1975
- Briefing Paper, House Subcommittee on Housing and Community Development, Oversight Hearings --, July 30, 1975
- Data Book for Oversight Hearings, Senate Committee on Banking, 11/5/
- Data Book, Secretary Hills, Hearings Before Subcommittee on Housing and Urban Affairs -- Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, Emergency Housing and Related Legislation, 3/17/75
- Data Book - Secretary Hills, Hearings Before the Joint Economic Committee -- Role of Housing in Economic Policy, (July 18, 1975)
- Department of Housing and Urban Development, Secretary's Briefing Book on Appropriations, (PROGRAM BOOK 1), March 1976
- Program Book 2 (Box 70)
- Program Book 3
- Program Book 4
- Program Book 5
- FY 1976 Hearings on HUD Appropriations
- Hearings on Condominiums -- Subcommittee on General Oversight and Renegotiation Postponed), (3-10-76
- Hearings on S.2986, Supplemental Employment Assistance, Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, 3/3/76 (Box 71)
- House Subcommittee on Housing and Community Development Hearings on the Housing Authorization Act of 1976, (March 2, 1976)
- House Committee on the Judiciary, Hearings Before Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights -, 9/30/76
- Joint Economic Committee Hearings, Outlook for the Housing Industry, (9/23/76)
- New Communities Administration, Briefing Materials for Senate Oversight Hearings on Outlook for Housing -, February 20, 1976
- New Communities Administration, Briefing Materials on Senate Oversight Hearings -- Fields of Housing/Community Development, (June 23, [UNK] (Box 72)
- Oversight Hearings on Outlook for Housing in Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, 1976 -- February 20, [UNK]
- Prepared Statement, Stevenson's Hearings re Chicago --, 7/14/75
- Section 202 Hearings, Subcommittee on Elderly Housing, Senate Select Committee on Aging, June 26, 1975
- Section 202 Elderly Housing Program -- Hearings Before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, 9/10/76
- Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs on S.2986, Supplemental Community Development Employment Assistance Act of 1976 (Counter-cyclical), March 3, 1976
- Senate Oversight Hearings -- Fields of Housing/Community Development, June 23, 1976
- Section 2273 -- Condominium Consumer Protection Act of 1975, Hearings Before the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, 10/6/75 (Box 73)
- Oversight Hearings, Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, 11/5/75
- Additional Budget Working Group Recommendations on FY 77 Budget
- Book #1 - FY 77 Budget Estimates/Principal Staff Requests
- Book #2 - FY 77 Budget Estimates/Principal Staff Requests
- Book #3 - FY 77 Budget Estimates/Principal Staff Requests (Box 74)
- Budget, 1975
- Operating Plan, 1976
- FY 77 Budget Press Briefing Questions and Answers
- CPD FY 77 Budget Recommendations
- HM FY 77 Budget Recommendations
- Department of Housing and Urban Development, Administration and Staff Resources, FY 77 Budget Recommendations
- Department of Housing and Urban Development, Fair Housing and Equal Opportunity, FY 77 Budget Recommendations
- Department of Housing and Urban Development, Office of General Counsel, FY 77 Budget Recommendations
- Department of Housing and Urban Development, General Departmental Management, FY 77 Budget Recommendations
- Department of Housing and Urban Development, Other Administration Issues, FY 77 Budget Recommendations
- Department of Housing and Urban Development, Policy Development and Research, FY 77 Budget Recommendations
- Department of Housing and Urban Development, Regional Management and Services, FY 77 Budget Recommendations
- Department of Housing and Urban Development FY 76 Appropriations Hearings Briefing Book (Box 75)
- FIA FY 77 Budget Recommendations
- Highlights on OMB Hearings on FY 77 Budget Estimates
- Highlights on OMB Hearings on FY 78 Budget Estimates
- Staff Recommendations/Comments on FY 77 Budget Estimates
- HPMC-FHA FY 77 Budget Recommendations
- NCA FY 77 Budget Recommendations
- The HUD Budget Transition Briefing Book --, March, 1975 (Box 76)
- CAH Telephone Notes Log
- Central City Insurance Practices
- Chicago Book I
- Chicago Book II
- Chicago Book III
- Community Development Block Grant Program, Briefing Book (Box 77)
- Community Planning and Development
- Community Planning and Development, Briefing Book
- Condominium Information
- Condominium Policy Options
- Condominiums
- Congressman Frank Horton, Meeting on Ganada New Community, 3/4/76
- Defaults -- Ballooning Book 1 (Box 78)
- Delegation of Authority
- Department of Housing and Urban Development, Secretary's Briefing Book, March 1976
- Deputy Under Secretary for Field Operations, Briefing Book
- Deputy Under Secretary for Management, Briefing Book
- Direct Cash Assistance Proposal, January 3, 1975
- District of Columbia Briefing Paper
- Democratic Research Organization -- Hearings Before the Committee To Investigate a Balanced Federal Budget, April 29, 1975
- DMI-75 Phase II Report on Community Planning and Development and Section 8 Process Analysis
- Domestic Council Briefing Book (Box 79)
- Draft, First Annual Report on Housing/Community Development Act
- Equal Opportunity
- Equal Opportunity Briefing Book
- Executive Resources Board Minutes
- Fair Housing and Affirmative Action (Background Materials)
- Federal Disaster Assistance Administration
- Federal Disaster Assistance Administration Briefing Book
- Federal Energy Administration
- Federal Insurance Administration Briefing Book
- Field Legal Services Handbook (Box 80)
- First Annual Report to Congress on Title VI of the Housing and Community Development Act of 1974 (Mobile Homes)
- Field - Problem Alerts
- Field - Problem Alerts
- Regions I and II - Boston and New York (Problem Alerts)
- Region III - Philadelphia (Problem Alerts)
- Region IV - Atlanta (Problem Alerts) (Box 81)
- Region V - Chicago (Problem Alerts)
- Region VI - Dallas (Problem Alerts)
- Regions VII and VIII - Kansas City and Denver (Problem Alerts)
- Regions IX and X - San Francisco and Seattle (Problem Alerts)
- Region V - H.R. Crawford (Box 82)
- Region VIII - Indian Program Status
- General Counsel
- General Counsel Briefing Book
- General Departmental Questions and Answers
- Government National Mortgage Association Briefing Book
- Government Operations Committee Report on Counseling
- HAP - Section 8 Task Force Housing
- Housing, Vol. #1, 6/16/76 through 9/30/76
- Housing - Volume II, 10/1/76 through 11/30/76 (Box 83)
- Housing - Volume III, 12/1/76 through January, 1977
- Housing Management, Volume I, 2/28/75 through 12/31/75
- Housing Management - Volume II, 1/2/76 through 6/11/76
- Housing Management Briefing Book
- Housing Needs (Box 84)
- HPMC Briefing Book
- HPMC Current Issues
- HPMC-FHA
- HPMC Principal Program Areas
- HUD/FNMA Liaison Meeting, July 6, 1976
- HUD Human Resources
- HUD Regional Office Telephone Director (Box 85)
- HUD Research Efforts
- Indian Task Force
- Indian Leaders Meeting, 3/10/76
- Inspector General
- Inspector General Briefing Book
- International Affairs Appendix to Briefing Book
- Interstate Land Sales Registration Briefing Book
- Invitations and Requests, March 10-April 30, 1975 (Box 86)
- Invitations and Requests, May 1-July 30, 1975
- Invitations and Requests, August 1-October, 1975
- Invitations and Requests, November 1975-February 1976
- Invitations and Requests, March-May, 1976 (Box 87)
- Invitations and Requests, June-September, 1976
- Invitations and Requests, October 1976-January 1977
- Labor Relations Briefing Book
- Lead-Based Paint Briefing Book
- Legislative Affairs Briefing Book
- Legislative History Block Grants
- Lubbock Insuring Office Director (Box 88)
- MAHA Briefing Book, with Gale Cincotta, 10/25/75
- Multifamily Defaults Book III
- National Corporation of Housing Partnerships
- New Communities
- New Communities Administration
- New Communities Questions and Answers
- New Communities Administration Board of Directors Meeting, July 10, 1975 (Box 89)
- New Communities Administration Board of Directors Meeting, August 4, 1976
- New Communities Board Book for Meeting, December 2, 1975
- New Communities Development Corporation Board of Directors Meeting, 12/2/75-1/26/76
- New Communities Board Book for Meeting, October 15, 1975
- New Communities Development Corporation Board of Directors Meeting, 3/16/76 (Box 90)
- New Communities Development Corporation Board of Directors Meeting, 6/24/76
- New Communities Development Corporation Board of Directors Meeting, 10/7/76
- New Communities Development Corporation Board of Directors Meeting, 11/16/76
- New Communities Development Corporation Board of Directors Meeting, 12/10/76 (Box 91)
- Undated New Communities Development Corporation Projects Book
- Newfields Briefing Book, 10/9/75
- Cedar-Riverside, Minneapolis, Minnesota and Jonathan-Chaska, Minnesot
- Gananda
- St. Charles -- Statutory Findings to Support Additional Guarantee Application
- Office of the Secretary -- Current Staff Resumes, February 21, 1975
- New Communities Board Book for Meeting, October 15, 1975 (Box 92)
- Organization
- PBWG Recommendations
- Pending Litigation Against HUD
- Policy Development and Research
- Presidential Q's and A's (Box 93)
- President Ford Committee Newsletters
- Property Disposition in Detroit
- Public Affairs
- Public Affairs Briefing Book
- PD&R Briefing Paper
- Proposed Consumer Representation Plan
- Park Forest South, 12/10/76
- Recruiting, Miscellaneous (Box 94)
- Recruiting, Assistant Secretary for HPMC-FHA
- Recruiting, FIA Administrator/OILSR Administrator
- Recruiting, Inspector General
- Recruiting, Consumer Affairs and Regulatory Functions
- Regulations/Issuances
- Report to Congress on Used Mobile Homes
- Report on Human Resources Management in HUD
- Savings and Loans -- New York State
- Section 8 Housing Mix Task Force
- Section 8, Rent Comparability (Box 95)
- Section 802, Briefing Book
- Section 848
- Semer and Zimmerman Study
- Seventh Annual Report on the National Housing Goal
- Starts for Individual SMSA's
- State of the Industry HUD Status and Trends
- State of the Union
- Statements and Witness Lists (Box 96)
- Strategy for Dealing with Multifamily Insured Defaults and Foreclosures
- Summaries and Reports on Investigations by Surveys and Investigation: Staff House Committee on Appropriations on the Regional and Area Office Structure and N/C Assistance
- US/USSR Joint Committee on Cooperation in the Field of Housing and Other Construction -- First Session, 6/16-19/75
- U.S. Conference of Mayors, Boston, Massachusetts -- Issues and Q's and A's, 7/8/75
- American Bar Association - Section of Antitrust Law Handbook
- New Communities Administration FY 77 Budget Recommendations
- New Communities Administration Board of Directors Meeting, July 10, 1975
- New Communities Board of Directors Meeting, August 5, 1976 (Box 97)
- A.M. Staff Meeting
- Acquired Inventory Book II
- Administration
- Administration - Briefing Book
- Administration, Vol. 2
- Federal Insurance Administration
- Business Conditions Reports (Box 98)
- Business Conditions Reports - Vol. #2
- Business Conditions Reports - Vol. #3
- Business Conditions Reports - Vol. #4
- Business Conditions Reports - Vol. #5
- Business Conditions Reports - Vol. #6 (Box 99)
- Business Conditions Reports - Vol. #7
- AGC Conference Programs, HUD Section 8 Conference, 8/10-11/76
- Financial Evaluation of Acquisition and Disposition Alternatives
- DMI - 75 Phase II
- ACKNOWLEDGEMENT LETTERS (Box 100)
  - A through R
- ACKNOWLEDGEMENT LETTERS (Box 101)
  - S through Z
- American Bar Association Journal (Box 102)
- American Bar Association - Antitrust Law Journal (Billings)
- American Bar Association - Antitrust Section Newsletter
- Nominating Committee - Antitrust Section - ARA
- ABA Proposed Publication Policy
- American Bar Association - Antitrust Law Journal Cumulative Index - Volumes 37
- ABA Annual Spring Meeting - Washington, D. C. Correspondence, 1974 April 4-5, 1974
- American Bar Association - Council Meetings Ocean Reef Club, Key Largo, Florida, 2/28-3/2/75
- ABA Antitrust Section - Miscellaneous Correspondence
- American Bar Association - Antitrust Developments Volume
- American Bar Association - Antitrust Developments Volume 43, Issue 4, 1973-1974
- American Bar Association - Mailing Lists
- American Bar Association, - Annual Meeting, Montreal, Quebec, 1975
- American Bar Association, - Post Montreal Meeting, LaChateau Montebello Hotel, Montebello, Canada, 8/13-17/75
- Legislation Committee, ABA - Section of Antitrust Law
- ABA Antitrust Section Council
- ABA Antitrust Section Council
- Chron - CAH -, March, 1975
- Chron - CAH -, February, 1975
- Chron - CAH -, January, 1975
- Chron - CAH -, December, 1974
- Chron - CAH -, October, 1974 (Box 103)
- Chron - CAH -, September, 1974
- Chron - CAH -, August, 1974
- Chron - CAH -, July, 1974